# Alix Reyna

Associate Project Manager

# **Personal Info**

**Address** 

UTC -05:00

**Phone** 

+52 834 301 1546

E-mail

alixreynaflo@gmail.com

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/alix-reyna-flores-744a6095

# Languages

English - Advanced

Spanish - Native

#### **Certificates**

2020-06

Certified Associate in Project Management (CAPM)

2019-02

Certificate in Full Stack Javascript Development

2017

ICAgile- ICP Agile Fundamentals

I am a PM with a focus on operations & logistics. I got my start in the world of Esports, first as a content collaborator for ESLA, and later as a logistics guru for Riot Games in the LATAM region. I love my work, because I am motivated by delivering magical customer experiences.

# **Experience**

**Vendor Management Specialist** 

2020-04 Riot Games - LATAM

I was primarily focused on supporting financial and legal operations and international logistics. As a certified full stack developer, I was also involved in advising the development of internal tools and processes that can help improve the employee experience when developing new projects and making purchasing decisions for the company.

2018-04 - **Office Coordinator** 

2018-12 Riot Games - LATAM

Over time, my responsibilities at the Riot Games LATAM office expanded to include support for the Santiago, Chile office. As Office Coordinator, I was tasked with providing logistics services that accommodated internal and player facing projects for multiple interdisciplinary teams in two offices across the LATAM region. My biggest project was the making of a documentary of amaizing LATAM players, where I managed logistics for the crew, while also serving as the influencers' travel logistics contact.

2016-05 - Office Assistant

2018-04 Riot Games - Latin America North

I originally joined Riot in an administrative role, where I was responsible for employee (rioter) travel and virtual live event logistics, legal documentation tracking and storage, and supported live events and larger multimedia campaigns. Favorite part of the job? I got to meet some of my favorite influencers and be their guide during esports events, cosplayer contests, and office visits.

2015 - **Content Collaborator** 

2016 Esports Latinoamerica (ESLA)

I got my start as a Content Collaborator, managing esports even logistics and coaching shoutcasters to improve their public speaking and presentation skills within the context of Esports hosting livestream. 5+ shoutcasters that I coached went onto bigger hosting opportunities at places like Riot Games, Activision Blizzard, Nintendo, and others.

# **Education**

2013 - **Universidad La Salle Victoria** - Cum Laude Bachelor's

I graduated with top honors in Communications Science, with a specialization on the effects of Mass Communication.